gooxinxin.com 2019-07-18

# Gooxinxin: Bikini,Dress,V-Neck,Polka Dot,Long Dress,Sleeveless Dress,T-Shirt,Chiffon Dress,Plus Size,Skirt

This is the Privacy Policy governing your use of the Gooxinxin.com Site. By using this Site, you approve and agree to our Privacy Policy set out below. All terms not defined in this document have the meanings ascribed to them in the Terms of Use Agreement between you and Gooxinxin.com which by use of this Site you agree to accept.

Your right to privacy is important to us. The following terms are provided to explain how we collect and use information about you so that you can make an informed choice about using the website. **  
**

 **Our Commitment to Privacy:**                                       

Gooxinxin.com respects the privacy of your information. Our Privacy Policy governs our online information practices and reflects our commitment to protect your privacy                                        

  **Security Measures:**                                       

Gooxinxin.com respects the privacy of your information. Our Privacy Policy governs our online information practices and reflects our commitment to protect your privacy

Your account information and profile are password protected.

Our personnel will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited e-mail. Remember to sign out of your account and close your browser window when you have finished your session

No data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be perfectly secured

 **Information Collection and Use:**                                       

Gooxinxin.com is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We attempt to keep this information, apart from whatever information is used to market your company to potential trading partners, private.

Gooxinxin.com does reserve the right to cooperate with law enforcement inquires and other third parties to enforce laws, intellectual property and other rights when, in its sole discretion, it believes in good faith such information is required   to assist such parties

 **Public Access to Information:**                                       

The information you provide will be made available to all users of our website. Please remember that any information you disclose becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose personally-identifying information

 **Disclosure of Information:**                                       

We reserve the right to disclose your information where we have reason to believe that such disclosure is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be infringing (or threatening to infringe) or who may otherwise be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our title, rights, interests or property or those of other website users or of anyone else who could be harmed by such activities

 **Co-Branded Relationships:**  

We have established relationships with other parties to offer you the benefit of  other products and services which we ourselves do not offer. We offer you access to these other parties either through the use of hyperlinks to their sites from our website, or through offering "co-branded" sites in which both ourselves and these other parties share the same URL, domain name or pages within a domain name  on the Internet. The Privacy Policy of such other parties may differ from ours.  We therefore encourage you to read that policy before responding of any offers,  products or services provided by such other parties

 **Accessing and Correcting Your Information:**  

You can access, view and edit your Registration Information, Publishing Information and Payment Information (if any) through your Account with Gooxinxin.com

 **Your Feedback:**  

Gooxinxin.com welcomes your continuous input regarding our Privacy Policy or our services provided to you

 **Contacting Us:**  

 If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us at: [[email protected]](http://www.gooxinxin.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)
